停!停止它!就这样停止吧!
Stop! Stop it! Just stop it!
——哎呀!——不!
- Agh! - No!
射她!射她!
Shoot her! Shoot her!
不!不要这样做!
Don't! Don't do it!
-布鲁克!-快他妈醒醒!
- Brooke! - Wake the fuck up!
给。
Here.
拿着。
Take it.
Grace……冷静。
Grace... Calm down.
离我们远点。
Stay the fuck away from us.
现在一切都好了，好吗?
Everything's alright now, OK?
她失控了，但现在没事了。
She lost it, but she's fine now.
一切都会好起来的，我保证。
Everything's gonna be alright, I promise you.
唉,
Agh!
不!
No!
让他们去。
Let 'em go.
你所有的怪物!
You're all monsters!
你们两个都是一样的。
You're both the fucking same.
你做了什么?
What have you done?
♬到城市的边缘走走
♪ Take a little walk to the edge of town ♪
♪穿过轨道♪
♪ Go across the tracks ♪
♬高架桥像一只厄运之鸟若隐若现
♪ Where the viaduct looms like a bird of doom ♪
♪随着它的移动和破裂
♪ As it shifts and cracks ♪
♬秘密就藏在边境的火海里
♪ Where secrets lie in the border fires ♪
♪在嗡嗡作响的电线里
♪ In the humming wires ♪
♬嘿，伙计，你知道你永远不会回来了
♪ Hey, man, you know you're never coming back ♪
♬过了广场，过了桥
♪ Past the square, past the bridge ♪
♬路过磨坊，路过栈
♪ Past the mills, past the stacks ♪
♪在一场暴风雨中，一个高大英俊的男人来了
♪ On a gathering storm comes a tall handsome man ♪
♬穿着满是灰尘的黑色外套，右手通红
♪ In a dusty black coat with a red right hand ♪
-♬他会把你搂在怀里……♪-好吧，来吧。
- ♪ He'll wrap you in his arms... ♪ - Alright, come on.
♪告诉你，你一直都是个好孩子
♪ Tell you that you've been a good boy ♪
♬他会重新点燃所有的梦想
♪ He'll rekindle all the dreams ♪
-♬你用了一辈子去摧毁…♬闭嘴。
- ♪ It took you a lifetime to destroy... ♪ - Shut up.
♬他会陷入深深的困境
♪ He'll reach deep in a hole ♪
-♬治愈你萎缩的灵魂……♪-嘿，别这样。
- ♪ Heal your shrinking soul... ♪ - Hey, come on.
♬但这并不是你能做的唯一一件事
♪ But there wont be a single thing that you can do ♪
♪他是神，他是人，他是鬼，他是大师
♪ He's a god, he's a man, he's a ghost, he's a guru ♪
♪他们在低语他的名字♪
♪ They're whispering his name ♪
-♬穿过这片正在消失的土地……♬准备好了吗?
- ♪ Through this disappearing land... ♪ - You all ready?
♪但他的外套里藏着一只红色的右手……♪
♪ But hidden in his coat is a red right hand... ♪
阿尔法探戈查理，我们有一辆向南行驶的车正接近44号横向路口。结束了。
Alpha Tango Charlie, we have a southbound vehicle approaching the 44 Lateral. Over.
收到，d0。
Roger that, Delta Zero.
我们在空中有一只眼在监视3-3-3 -12方向的44个侧翼。
We have an eye in the sky monitoring the 44 Lateral in the 3-3-12.
斑马旅馆，有一辆向北行驶的两轮车在23号公路上靠近。请证实。
Hotel Zebra, we have a northbound two-wheeler approaching on the 23 Parallel in Sector 1-1-38. Please confirm.
收到。
Roger that.
他妈的!
Fuck!
来吧,伙伴。
Come on, mate.
来吧。
Come on.
来吧。你得到的。
Come on. Out you get.
嘿!
Hey!
打开仓门!
Open bunker door!
啊,里斯!
Ah, Rhys!
所以…菜单上有什么?
So... what's on the menu?
我们发现一名男性，二十出头。
We've got a male, early 20s.
一些被关押在牢房里。有脑震荡的,也许。
Bit banged up. Concussed, maybe.
否则情况良好。
Otherwise good condition.
——把他。——是的,先生。
- Bring him. - Yes, sir.
在你的脚上。
On your feet.
哦,是的。
Oh, yes.
太棒了。
Fantastic.
优秀的骨骼结构。
Excellent bone structure.
真是个可爱的头骨。
That's one hell of a lovely skull.
-带他进去。——是的,先生。
- Get him inside. - Yes, sir.
好工作,里斯。做得很好。
Good work, Rhys. Well done.
你得到他了吗?
You got him?
正确的。正确的。
Right. Right.
在那里。在这里。正确的。
Over there. Over here. Right.
那我们找到治愈方法了吗?
So are we any closer to the cure?
当然了。
Yeah, of course we are.
混血儿被发现了，还有他弟弟。
The hybrid's been spotted, and the brother.
在哪里?
Where?
第八区，向北100公里。
Sector 8, 100 clicks to the north.
那另外两个呢?
And what about these other two?
谁在乎呢?
Who cares?
我们要的是怪物。
We want the freak.
混合。
The hybrid.
我们抓到那个女孩了。
We get the girl.
你得一枪崩了那个杀了你弟弟的混蛋。
You get to put a bullet in that prick who killed your brother.
啊…抽筋。是的。
Ugh... Cramp. Yeah.
我想是时候…再水化。
Guess it's time for me to... rehydrate.
——是的。-走吧。
- Yep. - Off you go.
啊，就在这儿。
Ah, just over here.
祝你好运，士兵。
Good luck out there, soldier.
现在，你把她活着带回来。
Now, you bring her in alive.
或者你不敲门。
Or you don't come knocking.
你得到我吗?
You get me?
是的。
Yeah.
群的枪手吗。
Pack of wankers.
关上仓门。
Close bunker door.
我们不该离开的。
We shouldn't have bloody left.
她扯断了我的喉咙，马克西。
She ripped my fuckin' throat out, Maxi.
你他妈在说什么?
What the fuck are you talking about?
那是谁的错?
Yeah, well whose fault was that?
我不会坐视她把别人折磨死的。
I'm not just gonna sit there and watch her torture some guy to death.
-那家伙是个士兵。——她生病了。
- That guy was a soldier. - She's sick.
她的情况越来越糟。
And she's getting worse.
她和她哥哥。
Her and her brother.
他们已经疯了。
They've gone road crazy.
我们不能再相信他们了。
We can't trust 'em no more.
本尼叔叔信任他们。
Uncle Benny trusted 'em.
本尼叔叔的死。
Uncle Benny's dead.
恩典吗?
Grace?
他妈的。
Fuck.
来，张开你的嘴。
Here, open your mouth.
在这里。在这里,在这里。打开,打开!
Here. Here, here. Open, open!
你对吧?
You alright?
在这里。
Here.
让我们走了。
Let's get going.
嗨。
Hi.
不!不，不，不!
No! No, no, no, no, no!
安静!
Quiet!
哦……授予访问权限。
Oh... Access granted.
好,好,好。
Well, well, well.
我告诉过你，我工作的时候不要带任何人进来。
I told you never to bring anybody in here while I'm working.
看来你是对的，警官。
Turns out you were right, Sergeant.
看来我们的卫生局局长有个藏牙的。
Looks like our Surgeon General here's a bite-hider.
你他妈的。
You fuck.
-把你的枪拿出来。——是的,上校。
- Unholster your weapon. - Yes, Colonel.
走在那里。
Walk over there.
-一枪爆了他的头——是的,先生。
- And blow his brains out. - Yes, sir.
稍等一下。
Just hang on a minute.
只是…只是等待!
Just... Just wait!
你得掩饰一下你的症状。
You need to hide your symptoms better.
是,……真的有必要吗?
Was that... ..really necessary?
你要是再把我置于那种境地…我一枪崩了你的脑袋。
You ever put me in a position like that again... I'll put a bullet through your fuckin' skull.
是的，但是... ..你从哪儿弄来的药，上校?
Yes, but then... ..where would you get your medicine from, Colonel?
我们这个月的血清量不够了。
We're not going to make our serum quota this month.
总部会开始调查的。
HQ's gonna start asking questions.
他妈的总部。
Fuck HQ.
而且，一旦我们抓到她…
And besides, once we get our hands on her...
．．我们不用再担心这个了。
..we won't have to worry about that anymore.
唉,
Agh!
等等!等等，等等，等等，等等!
Wait! Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
他妈的耶稣基督。
Jesus fucking Christ.
你是一个杂种。
You're a hybrid.
什么他妈的!
What the fuck!
打开仓门!
Open bunker door!
他妈的白痴。
Fuckin' idiots.
现在就动手有点晚了，不是吗?
It's a bit late for a barrel drop, ain't it?
这不关你的事，冠军。
It's not your concern, champ.
Oi !Oi !我需要那该死的燃料，你们这群白痴。
Oi! Oi! I need that fuckin' fuel for the barrel drop, you fuckin' idiots.
我需要你在这，下士。
I need you right here, Corporal.
是的,先生。
Yes, sir.
交货是什么?
What's the delivery?
女性。20岁出头。
Female. Early 20s.
她是一个混合。
She's a hybrid.
现在去找她。
Go get her now.
-是长官-是上校
- Yes, sir. - Yes, Colonel.
他妈的!基督!
Fuck! Christ!
射死她的腿。
Oh, shoot her fuckin' legs out.
嘿,嘿,嘿!等等，等等，等等。
Hey, hey, hey! Wait, wait, wait, wait.
我可以让她冷静下来。我可以让她冷静下来。
I can calm her down. I can calm her down.
让她还。
Keep her still.
别动，别动。
Hold still, hold still.
给你，亲爱的，给你，给你。
Here you go, hon. Here you go, here you go.
那就这样吧。那就这样吧。
There you go. There you go.
放松。
Easy.
一切都会好的。
It's gonna be alright.
我保证。
I promise.
-带她进去。——是的,先生。
- Get her inside. - Yes, sir.
哦，把它放下，你他妈的白痴。
Oh, put it down, you fuckin' idiot.
Oi。Oi !
Oi. Oi!
我想知道这个人是怎么回事。
I want to know what goes on with this one.
如果她是治愈方法的关键，我想知道。
If she's a key to the cure, I want to know.
你上你的卡车。
You get in your truck.
像个好士兵一样放下枪，滚远点。
You drop your barrels like a good little soldier and fuck off.
关上仓门!
Close bunker door!
哦,妈的…现在我他妈的没油了，不是吗?
Oh, for fuck's... Now I've run out of fuckin' fuel, haven't I?
啊,他妈的!来吧!来吧，你他妈的…
Ah, the fuck! Come on! Come on, you fuckin'...
给你。给你。
Here you go. Here you go.
这就对了，伙计。他妈的吃!
There you go, mate. Fuckin' eat!
Nuh。他妈的……来吧，你这该死的东西。
Nuh. Fuckin'... Come on, you fuckin' thing.
嘿?来吧!
Hey? Come on!
来吧!
Come on!
来吧，你们这群混蛋在哪儿?
Come on, where are you, you bastards?
快来，快来拿!
Come on, come and get it!
得到一些肉!
Get some meat!
来吧，你们这些臭动物!
Come on, ya stinkin' fuckin' animals!
快来拿!
Come and get it!
好吧。又来了，嘿?
Alright. Here we go, hey?
来吧。
Come on.
就是这样。来吧,伙伴。
That's it. Come on, mate.
不,操。
Nah, fuck this.
别动，你这该死的东西!有丫。
Stay still, ya fuckin' thing! There ya go.
加油！加油
Come on, come on.
是的!
Yes!
我明天再来接你，伙计。
I'll come back for you tomorrow, mate.
来人是谁?
Who goes there?
嘿，别对着我，你个混蛋。
Hey, not on me, you fuckin' peanut.
耶稣基督。
Jesus Christ.
我有桶给你。
I got barrels for ya.
哈!该死的警察，你们这些婊子!
Ha! Fuckin' cop that, ya cunts!
他妈的,是的。
Fuck, yeah.
他妈的猫咪。
Fuckin' pussy.
你是一个白痴。
You're an idiot.
喂!。
G'day.
这个是去地堡的吗?
Is this one for the bunker?
这是为了掩体里的孩子们，对吗?
That for the boys in the bunker, is it?
好。桶在后面。
Righto. Barrels are in the back.
是的,先生。
Yes, sir.
白痴。
Dickhead.
他妈的。
Fuck.
等待。等等，等等，等等!
Wait. Wait, wait, wait, wait!
-等等，等等，不，不，不!——不要动!
- Wait, wait, wait, no, no, no! - Hold still!
都撑不过去了。
Not even gonna make it.
他妈的下地狱!
Fuckin' hell!
他妈的!来吧!
Fuck! Come on!
嘿!你好!
Hey! Hello!
对，对，对，看这个!
Yes, yes, yes, look at this!
嘿?快点，抓住它!
Hey? Come on, get it!
他妈的!
Fuck!
我想让你用鼻子深吸一口气，想象一束蓝色的治疗光深入你的头顶脉轮。
I want you to take a deep breath in through your nose and visualise a stream of blue healing light travelling deep into your crown chakra.
这种能量会进入你的整个大脑……
This energy travels down into your whole head...
．．神圣的愈合……
..sacred healing...
哦,他妈的!
Oh, fuck!
他妈的!
Fuck!
让你的整个生命从恐惧中解脱出来。
Let your entire being be free from fear.
与宇宙完全和平相处。
and completely at peace with the universe.
哇,放松!
Whoa, easy. Easy, easy!
你要在这里告诉我你要帮我找回我妹妹。
This is where you tell me you're gonna help me get my sister back.
不然我就用枪射穿你的脑袋。
Or I'll put this dart through your fuckin' head.
确定。
Sure.
你妹妹是谁?
Who's your sister?
我和你去兜兜风。
Me and you are going for a drive.
你得去看看你的伤口。
You'll have to get that wound looked at.
如果你离开那里，你会得败血症，然后死掉。
If you leave that you'll get septicaemia and you'll die.
是的,对的。
Yeah, right.
我所要做的就是放了你，好吗?
And all I have to do is cut you loose, yeah?
听着，我相信我们有办法解决这个问题让我们彼此信任。
Listen, I'm sure there's some way we can work this out where we can both trust each other.
听着,你会……你能把手指从扳机上拿开吗?
Listen, would you... Would you mind taking your finger off that trigger there?
闭嘴，缝合。
Shut up and stitch.
我这样做。
I'm doing it.
举起手来。
Get your hands up.
——举起手来!——它们。
- Hands up! - They're up.
他妈的下地狱。神。
Fuckin' hell. God.
启动发动机。
Start the engine.
停止。
Stop.
好了，我们开始吧。
OK, off we go.
我们必须打开大门。
We have to open the gate.
击穿。
Smash through it.
我们会直接弹开，你的脸会撞到仪表盘上。
We'll bounce straight off and you're gonna smash your face on the dashboard.
不,这是废话。
Nah, that's bullshit.
你只是不想把你的小门弄乱。
You just don't want to mess up your nice little gate.
这是你的电话。
It's your call.
这样做。
Do it.
漂亮的卡车。
Nice truck.
不跟我说话?
Not talking to me, huh?
随便你。
Suit yourself.
那是什么?
What's that?
它看起来像什么?
What does it look like?
他们的药。
They're pills.
抗病毒药物。
Anti-viral pills.
这是我在这里生存的方式。
It's how I stay alive up here.
你为什么拿着这个?
Why have you got this?
因为他们是恐怖分子。他们是杀手。
'Cause they're terrorists. They're killers.
你不就是这么做的吗?
Ain't that what you do?
不，那不是我的工作。
No, that's not what I do.
我看过尸体。
I've seen the bodies.
你绑架人，然后杀了他们!
You kidnap people and you kill 'em!
我们不杀人。
We don't kill anybody.
-有我们的包裹吗?-是的。
- You got a package for us? - Yeah.
那是混血女孩的妹妹。
It's the hybrid girl's sister.
没有大便。
No shit.
你可真忙，里斯。
You've been a busy boy, Rhys.
好了,伙计。
Well played, mate.
-去找她。——是的,先生。
- Go and get her. - Yes, sir.
他妈的!他妈的……
Fuck! Fuckin'...
嘿!嘿，放轻松，伙计。她是个该死的孩子。
Hey! Hey take it easy, mate. She's a fuckin' kid.
不管怎样，这个小混蛋都会死在木桶里。
Either way, this little prick's gonna end up in a fuckin' barrel.
你说什么，伙计?
What'd you say, mate?
"不管怎样，她最后都会死在桶里"这他妈是什么意思?
"Either way, she ends up in a barrel"? What the fuck does that mean?
意思是上车开走，下士。
It means get in your vehicle and drive away, Corporal.
上你的车。
Get in your vehicle.
车程。
Drive away.
好。
Righto.
哇。他妈的怎么回事?
Whoa. What the fuck just happened?
上车。
Get in the truck.
他妈的!
Fuck!
大便。狗屎!
Shit. Shit!
——屎!-硝基激活。
- Shit! - Nitro activated.
操的缘故。
Fuck's sakes.
——电源启动。——加油!' !他妈的' !
- Power priming. - Come on! Prime! Fuckin' prime!
——甲烷低。—更换电源。
- Methane low. - Replace power source.
别担心。他们没有硝基。
Don't worry. They don't have nitro.
你确定吗?
You sure about that?
他妈的狗屎! !
Fuckin' shit!!
Wakey-wakey !
Wakey-wakey!
去他妈的抓狗!
Fuckin' get the dog!
——吃到坚果了!——牛眼灯!
- - Got the nuts! - Bullseye!
感觉怎么样，猛男?
How's that feel, slugger?
感觉不太好，是吧?
Doesn't feel too good, does it, hey?
他妈的疼。
Fuckin' hurts.
你看，在这里叛国者是会被判死刑的，下士。
See, traitors get the death penalty around here, Corporal.
我认为……任何一个在别人倒下时踢他蛋蛋的人... ..不应该让一个士兵去死。
I reckon... any man who kicks another man in the balls when he's down... ..don't deserve a soldier's death.
你哥哥死得很有尊严。
See, your brother, he died with dignity.
荣誉。
Honour.
像个真正的男人。
Like a real man.
但你不是一个真正的男人，对吧，嘿?
But you're not a real man, are ya, hey?
你是一只狗。
You're a dog.
你这个卑鄙下流的家伙。
You're a lowdown, dirty dog.
你会像条狗一样死去。
And you're gonna die like a fuckin' dog.
看到这些老家伙了吗，蹑手蹑脚的?
You see these old boys, creeping up?
他们几分钟后就到。
They'll be here in a couple of minutes.
等他们来了，他们会把你的脚全吃了。
And when they get here, they're gonna eat you from the feet up.
首先你的脚。
First your feet.
然后你的腿。
Then your legs.
你的球。
Your balls.
这个顺序。
In that order.
像你这样的大块头。
Big tough guy like you.
他们咬你的时候你可能还活着。
You could still be alive when they get to your guts.
你现在过得不错吧?
You have a good one now, eh?
好,好,好。
Well, well, well.
看看谁来了?
Look what the cat's dragged in, eh?
除非我搞错了，我们不是已经处理好这坨屎了吗?
Unless I'm mistaken didn't we take care of this piece of shit already?
那是我弟弟。
That was my brother.
你的兄弟吗?
Your brother?
所以双胞胎吗?
So twins?
你的兄弟,不是吗?
Your brother, eh?
他是个混蛋，罪有应得。
He was a fuckwit who got exactly what he deserved.
我要杀了你。
I'm gonna kill ya.
不,伴侣。
Nah, mate.
不，你唯一要做的就是坐在那里流血直到我他妈的命令你!
No, the only thing you're gonna do is sit there and bleed until I fuckin' say so!
是你在路上撞坏了他们的车。
You were the one that crashed their rig on the road.
你把格蕾西交给了地堡里的那些屠夫。
You gave Gracie to those butchers in the bunker.
再一次…马克西还告诉我你救了她的命。
Then again... Maxi also tells me you saved her life.
不过，我还是不知道。
Still, I don't know.
你身上有某种东西。
There's just something about ya.
他的脸。
His face.
我讨厌这张脸!
I hate this face!
就是这样。的脸。
That's it. The face.
脸是一个真正的问题。
The face is a real problem.
我真想把它扯下来吃掉。
I just wanna rip it off and eat the fuckin' thing.
你觉得呢，马克西?
What do you think, Maxi?
这家伙是朋友还是狗粮?
Is this guy a friend or is he dog food?
狗粮。
Dog food.
你说呢，大兵?
What do you say, soldier boy?
你是我们的朋友还是我把你的脸咬下来?
You our friend or do I bite your face off?
我是你的朋友。
I'm a friend, yeah.
绝对的朋友。
Definitely the friend.
里面有多少人?
How many men in there?
五个
Five.
两个在前门，两个带枪，还有一个医生。
Two out front and two with guns and a medic.
-他们的硬件呢?-还是老样子。
- And their hardware? - Just the usual.
斯太尔，猎枪，格洛克手枪，手榴弹。
Steyrs, shotguns, Glocks, grenades.
如果我们抢先一步，这些都不重要了。
If we get the drop on them, none of that'll matter.
我们将送他们。
We'll take 'em.
Oi。
Oi.
你放了我，我可以保证。
You cut me loose, I can guarantee that.
咳嗽得很厉害。
Bit of a nasty cough.
你有点骗子，是吗?
You a bit crook, are ya?
找这些吗?
Looking for these?
是什么在他们吗?
What's in 'em?
我他妈的不知道。
I don't fuckin' know.
给他吧。
Give 'em to him.
啊,操。
Ah, fuck it.
哦,你他妈的!
Oh, you fuck!
你怎么能做到呢?
How can you do it?
我不知道。
I didn't know.
你什么意思，你不知道?
What do you mean, you didn't know?
我不知道他们要杀他们。我…——废话。-你以为我在乎你的想法吗，亲爱的?
I didn't know they were killing them. I... - Bullshit. - You think I give a fuck what you think, love?
-布鲁克…——你知道!
- Brooke... - You knew!
你们都好吗?
You all good?
你能把我们弄进去吗?
You reckon you can get us in there?
放松。
Easy.
什么……?
What the...?
——入侵者!-我们被攻击了!
- Intruders! - We're under attack!
-我们被包围了!——下来!
- We've been surrounded! - Get down!
你的朋友吗?
Friend of yours?
几天前我把他接走了。
I picked him up a couple of days ago.
离这儿不远。
Not far from here.
现在你知道了。
Now you know.
你用它们做什么?
What do you do with them?
在地下掩体里?
Down in the bunkers?
我们在他们体内培育一种治疗血清，然后提取出来。
We grow a curative serum inside them and then extract it.
这血清。治疗的人吗?
And this serum. It cures people?
不治疗。管理。这是预防。
Not cures. Manages. It's preventative.
防止病毒蔓延
Keeps the virus from taking hold.
听着我有足够你用一年的医疗用品
Listen, I have medical supplies that could last you a year.
数百发子弹。
Hundreds of rounds of ammunition.
炸药。手榴弹,伴侣。任何你想要的。
Explosives. Grenades, mate. Whatever you want.
为什么桶?
Why the barrels?
你应该知道。
You should know.
我们把它们磨碎，然后把它们变成粉末。
We grind 'em up then convert them to powder form.
药片。
Pills.
我们做药。
We make pills.
Oi !
Oi!
走开，我就打爆他的头!
Move and I'll blow his fuckin' head off!
这些……诅咒……他们夺走了我的灵魂。
These... fucks... .. they took my soul.
所以我要和你一起去那个地堡我们要把那些狗娘养的杀个精光。
And so I am gonna go down into that bunker with you and we're gonna kill every last one of those sons-of-bitches.
我要弥补这一切。
I gotta make this right.
他妈的。
Fuckin' A.
上校。你还好吗?
Colonel. You OK?
我很好。
I'm fine.
你好吗?
You fine?
去检查周边!
Go and check the perimeter!
授予访问权限。
Access granted.
啊,上校!要不要来一声?
Ah, Colonel! Care for a toot?
没有?不,不。等等!
No? No, no. Wait!
事情没那么简单。
It's not that simple.
你不能像我们对其他人那样把她吸出来。
You just can't suck it out of her like we do with the others.
这就像给火箭注入燃料一样。
That would be like injecting rocket fuel.
楼上有情况，上校。
We have a situation upstairs, Colonel.
哦,操我。
Well, fuck me.
花的时间太长了。
It's taking too long.
什么是错的。
Something's wrong.
不可能。给它一些时间。
No way. Give it time.
我们开始吧。来吧!
Here we go. Come on!
好了，开始吧。
Alright, here we go.
-来吧，准备好。另一个失望。-压制你的火力!
- Come on, get ready. Another one down. - Suppress your fire!
大便。狗屎!
Shit. Shit!
里斯。
Rhys.
走吧!走，走，走，走!
Go! Go, go, go, go!
利马祖鲁老爹，22号公路发生187起事故。
Lima Papa Zulu, we have a 187 on the 22.
请求连接，完毕。
Requesting a link-up, over.
维克多·基洛·英迪亚，一辆房车被困在93度线上。
Victor Kilo India, we have a trapped RV in the 93 Parallel.
请求立即直升机。
Requesting immediate choppers.
你带她。我找到了他弟弟和送货员。
You take her. I got the brother and the delivery boy.
是的。是的,同意了。
Yeah. Yeah, agreed.
在我回来之前，你去找她... ..我要杀了你。
You start on her before I get back... ..I'll fuckin' kill ya.
噢,是吗?就像你杀了里斯一样?
Oh, yeah? Like you killed Rhys?
请原谅我没吓得发抖。
Well, forgive me if I'm not trembling in my booties.
这他妈是什么玩意?
Whoa, what the fuck is this shit?
别担心。
Don't worry.
它是一种清洁剂。它能杀死病毒
It's a cleansing agent. It kills the virus.
它是用什么做的?
What's it made out of?
保持安静。他们正在下来。
Stay quiet. They're coming down now.
她还活着。
She's alive.
把门打开。
Get that door open.
他妈的!噢!
Fuck! Ow!
-那是什么鬼东西?——对不起。
- What the fuck was that? - Sorry.
哦,操我。
Oh, fuck me.
拒绝访问。
Access denied.
好的。
OK.
你好,男孩。
G'day, boys.
下降。
Drop 'em.
不然我就打爆她的头。
Or I'll blow her fuckin' head off.
所有的他们。
All of 'em.
现在踢翻他们。
Now kick 'em over.
好小伙子。
Good lads.
嘿!
Hey!
他妈的软弱……哦!
Weak fuckin'... Ohh!
就是这个混蛋杀了你弟弟?
This the prick who killed your brother?
这么想的。
Thought so.
你看，如果某个肮脏的混蛋杀了我弟弟，我一定会好好地，慢慢地干掉他。
Now, you see, if some dirty bastard killed my brother, I'd make sure I'd do him nice and slow.
你好,亲爱的!
Hello, toots!
你介不介意我敲开你的头骨享用里面的果汁?
Would you mind if I cracked open your skull and feasted on the juice inside?
你在干什么，大块头?嗯?
What are you up to, big guy? Huh?
难道你不知道一个人的肠子都挂在外面了应该有足够的理智去死!
Don't you know that a bloke with his guts hanging on the outside should have enough sense to fuckin' die!
应急电源激活。
Emergency power activated.
唉,
Agh!
1138号，我们刚从5B药厂过来那边是个该死的屠宰场。
1138, we just came from Pill Factory 5B and it's a fuckin' slaughterhouse over there.
你们今天在你们的区域遇到什么麻烦了吗?
Did you guys have any trouble in your sector today?
马上给我滚过来!
Get your arses up here now!
别为我担心。
Don't worry about me.
我们得把门打开。
We need to get that door open.
布鲁克,你行吗?
Brooke, you OK?
布鲁克?
Brooke?
哦，该死，这可不好。
Oh, shit, that's not good.
等等，别开枪。
Wait, don't shoot her.
那我他妈该怎么办?
What the fuck do I do, then?
进入!快!
Get in! Quick!
快!快!
Quick! Quick!
该死的地狱。
Fucking hell.
笼子门撑不住了!
That cage door's not gonna hold!
现在给我一小瓶血。
Give me a blood vial now.
——大便。——加油!
- Shit. - Come on!
大便。他们了。
Shit. They're cracked.
-所有人!——哦,…他妈的!
- All of 'em! - Oh, for... Fuck!
所以只有血能让她平静下来，对吧?
So it's just blood that calms her down, right?
这是正确的。
That's right.
我有个主意。
I think I have an idea.
是啊，你当然知道。
Yeah, 'course you do.
走吧!
Go!
唉,
Agh!
带你妹妹离开这里。
Get your sister out of here.
没关系。
It's OK.
帮助我。
Help me up.
他妈的。
Fuck.
回来!
Get back!
你对吧?
You right?
你他妈的!
You fuck!
自毁的启动序列。
Self-destruct sequence initiated.
你们有30秒撤离。
You have 30 seconds to evacuate.
去电梯那里。
Get to the elevator.
拒绝访问。
Access denied.
自毁的启动序列。
Self-destruct sequence initiated.
拒绝访问。
Access denied.
什么他妈的!
What the fuck!
你们有20秒撤离。
You have 20 seconds to evacuate.
自毁的启动序列。
Self-destruct sequence initiated.
你在干什么?
What are you doing?
进去。现在!
Get in. Now!
- - - - - -来吧。——不!
- Come on. - No!
等待。你呢?
Wait. What about you?
保证她的安全。
Keep her safe.
你们有10秒钟撤离。
You have 10 seconds to evacuate.
九个
Nine.
八个
Eight.
七。
Seven.
六。
Six.
五个
Five.
四。
Four.
三。
Three.
两个。
Two.
一个。
One.
自毁了。再见。
Self-destruct initiated. Goodbye.
他要带格蕾丝去哪?
Where's he taking Grace?
搜索的地方。
Search the place.
找到它。
Find it.
他妈的!
Fuck!
我们该怎么办?
What are we gonna do?
哦,是的。
Oh, yes.
嘿!嘿。
Hey! Hey.
来吧,伙伴。
Come on, mate.
他妈的!
Fuck!
是的。
Yes.
把目光移开。
Look away.
啊,操。
Ah, fuck.
开始了，伙计。
Here we go, mate.
早餐时间到了，走吧。
Brekkie time, come on.
给你。
Here you go.
这就对了，伙计。走了。
There you go, mate. Go.
是的!
Yes!
唉,
Agh!
嘿。你。
Hey. You.
过来把这个塞进我的鼻子里。
Come and stick this up my nose.
把它塞进鼻子里?
Stick it up your nose?
为什么?
Why?
你他妈别问为什么，你个傻逼!
Don't you fucking question why, you dumb sonofabitch!
你拿着这该死的插管插进我的鼻子里!
You just take this fucking cannula and you stick it up my nose!
我将这样做。
I'll do it.
好的，等一下。别他妈这么粗暴。
OK, wait a minute. Just don't be so fucking rough.
只是不要太远!
Just not too far!
我他妈就知道!这家伙是一个咬藏者!
I fucking knew it! This guy's a bite-hider!
唉,
Agh!
留下来。
Stay.
啊,里斯。
Ah, Rhys.
看到你这样我真的很难过。
It actually does pain me to see you like this.
我真的不能告诉你…
And I really can't tell you...
．．我有多后悔杀了你
..how much I'm gonna regret killing you.
毕竟……我欠你一条命!
After all... .. I owe you my life!
是你，里斯，让我活着……
It was you, Rhys, who kept me alive...
整整一年。
for a full year.
你真是个优秀的送货员。
You were such a good delivery boy.
去你妈的!
Fuck you!
这是最可怕的事情。
It's the darndest thing.
你知道我闻到了什么吗，里斯?
You know what I can smell, Rhys?
我从没想过会在你身上闻到这种味道，小家伙。
Something I never, ever thought I would smell on you, little man.
大脑。
Brains.
我要砸碎你的头骨，挖出你的脑浆吃了，快递员!
I'm gonna crush your skull, scoop out your brains and eat them, delivery boy!
你把他们。
You take 'em.
你一直在吃。
And you keep taking 'em.
你要帮我们。
And you're gonna help us.
这样才能找回你的灵魂。
That's how you get your soul back.